# **侯璐**。 个人简历

## 博士研究

"面向车联网的移动云网络资源管理与优化研究",来自"国家 自然科学基金项目"

My research examined the use of ELW pulses from a mode-locked source array inducted through transuranic crystals to observe entanglement on supraquantum structures. Theoretical advancements included prediction of quantum resonance phenomena including the possibility of resonance cascades. I was motivated to conduct this doctoral research due to my passion for teleportation of matter and I believe I have laid the foundation for further experimental validation and development of practical outcomes.

# 主要研究方向

物联网云平台 LORA系统 车联网

## 项目经历

SEP. 2014 - JUN. 2015 (c)

IEEE 802.IIp 协议栈与应用开发

开发者

参与开发了车联网 IEEE 802.IIP 通信协议的协议栈,并在 ARM 开发板上实现了碰撞预警等应用。

SEP. 2016 - NOW (NODE.JS)

## 物联网云平台设计与实现 副团队领导人

This position involved transitioning from purely theoretical work to experimental applications utilising the immense resources of Black Mesa. The transition required an initial learning curve in hazard containment, health and safety procedures and operating experimental infrastructure. Manipulating valves, carts, buttons, levers, etc considerably increased my physical fitness.

OCT. 2017 - NOW (NODE.JS)

LoRa 系统设计与实现 团队领导人

设计

SEP. 2015 - NOW (PYTHON)

车联网资源分配算法研究 个人

# 已发表论文

 Kan Zheng, Lu Hou, Hanling Meng, Qiang Zheng, Ning Lu, Lei Lei, "Soft-defined heterogeneous vehicular network: architecture and challenges," *IEEE Network*, vol. 30, no. 4, July 2016, pp. 72-80.(IF = 7.23)  北京市海淀区西土城路10号

+86-15501081468

houlu8674@bupt.edu.cn

https://www.houlu.me https://github.com/houluy

https://www.linkedin.com/in/houlu

guaguade
stroooooo

0

## 教育经历

2014 - 2019 工学博士

智能计算与通信实验室

北京邮电大学

2010 - 2014 工学学士

信息与通信工程学院

北京邮电大学

JUNE 2019 毕业

北京邮电大学

## 获奖情况

2017 国家奖学金

北京邮电大学智能计算与通信实验室

2018 北京邮电大学博士生创新基金资助项目 北京邮电大学智能计算与通信实验室

2018 第二届良飞奖

北京邮电大学智能计算与通信实验室

## 计算机技能

精通 Office,

熟悉 Linux,

## 编程技能

精通 Python , Node.js

熟悉 C, C++, MATLAB, LATEX, SQL shell, HTML, Javascript, CSS

了解 Go, Rust, lisp, Java

## 英语技能

具有熟练地听、说、读、写的英语能力

# 技能

Goal Oriented

I believe in action over long-winded discussions. I listen to everyone's viewpoints and use my judgement to immediately act based on consensus to achieve goals quickly and efficiently.

Physical Dexterity

Manual manipulation of experimental equipment and training within Black Mesa (e.g. the Hazard Course) have contributed to an enjoyment of working with my hands.

Passionate

- 2. Lu Hou, Shaohang Zhao, Xiong Xiong, Kan Zheng, Periklis Chatzimisios, M. Shamim Hossain, Wei Xiang, "Internet of things cloud: architecture and implementation," *IEEE Communications Magazine*, vol. 54, no. 12, Dec. 2016, pp. 32-39. (IF = 10.435)
- **3. Lu Hou**, Shaohang Zhao, Xing Li, Periklis Chatzimisios, Kan Zheng, "Design and implementation of application programming interface for Internet of things cloud," *International Journal of Network Management*, vol. 27, no. 3, June 2016. (IF = 1.118)
- **4. Lu Hou**, Kan Zheng, Periklis Chatzimisios, Yi Feng, "A continuoustime Markov decision process-based resource allocation scheme in vehicular cloud for mobile video services," *Computer Communications*, vol. 118, Mar. 2018, pp. 140-147. (IF = 3.338)
- **5. Lu Hou**, Lei Lei, Kan Zheng, "Design on publish/subscribe message dissemination for vehicular networks with mobile edge computing," *2017 IEEE GLOBECOM*, Dec. 2017
- 6. Xiong Xiong, Lu Hou, Kan Zheng, Wei Xiang, M. Shamim Hossain, and Sk Md Mizanur Rahman, "SMDP-based radio resource allocation scheme in software-defined internet of things networks," *IEEE Sensors Journal* vol. 16, no. 20, June 2016, pp. 7304-7314. (IF = 2.512)
- 7. Xiong Xiong, **Lu Hou**, Long Zhao, "A Group-Based Massive Multiple Access Scheme in Cellular M2M Networks," *Computer Communications*, vol. 121, May. 2018, pp. 44-49. (IF = 3.338)

I have been interested in theoretical physics such as quantum mechanics and relativity from an early age. My education and research have cemented this interest into a passion. I greatly enjoy carrying out fundamental physics research with potential practical applications.



#### DOCTORAL RESEARCH

"Research on Resource Management and Optimization of Mobile Cloud Networks for Internet of Vehicles" from *The* National Natural Science Foundation of China

My research examined the use of ELW pulses from a mode-locked source array inducted through transuranic crystals to observe entanglement on supraquantum structures. Theoretical advancements included prediction of quantum resonance phenomena including the possibility of resonance cascades. I was motivated to conduct this doctoral research due to my passion for teleportation of matter and I believe I have laid the foundation for further experimental validation and development of practical outcomes.

## MAJOR RESEARCH DIRECTIONS

INTERNET OF THINGS CLOUD LORA SOLUTIONS VEHICULAR NETWORKS

## PROJECT EXPERIENCES

CURRENT, FROM JAN 1995 (FT)

# Black Mesa Research Facility *Team Leader (Anomalous Materials)*

As part of this promotion, I began conducting nuclear and subatomic research in the Anomalous Materials department. My team and I are particularly interested in dimensionality and its interaction with spacetime. The focus is on practical outcomes and applications in teleportation and communication with distal locations.

FEB 1991 – JAN 1995 (FT)

# Black Mesa Research Facility Level 3 Research Associate

This position involved transitioning from purely theoretical work to experimental applications utilising the immense resources of Black Mesa. The transition required an initial learning curve in hazard containment, health and safety procedures and operating experimental infrastructure. Manipulating valves, carts, buttons, levers, etc considerably increased my physical fitness.

JUL 1982 – DEC 1984 (PT)

# WashPests Limited Pest Control Technician

In this summer job I was tasked with helping eradicate pests from industrial areas. Work involved setting traps, spraying and physical eradication. I received praise for reaching difficult areas and my innovative use of a crowbar to assist in my work.

No. 10, Xitucheng Road, Beijing
+86-15501081468
houlu8674@bupt.edu.cn
https://www.lucima.cn
https://github.com/username
https://www.linkedin.com/in/username
guaguade

#### **EDUCATION**

තී

astroooooo

2014 – 2019 Doctor of Philosophy
 Intell. Comput. and Commun. Lab Beijing Univ. of Posts and Telecom.

 2010 – 2014 Bachelor of Engineering
 School of Inform. and Commun. Eng. Beijing Univ. of Posts and Telecom.

 JUNE 2019 Graduation
 Beijing Univ. of Posts and Telecom.

### **AWARDS**

2017 China National Scholarship
Intell. Comput. and Commun. Lab
Beijing Univ. of Posts and Telecom.

2018 BUPT Excellent Ph.D. Students Foundation Intell. Comput. and Commun. Lab Beijing Univ. of Posts and Telecom.

2018 2<sup>th</sup> LiangFei Scholarship
Intell. Comput. and Commun. Lab
Beijing Univ. of Posts and Telecom.

### PROGRAMMING SKILLS

EXPERT Python →, Node.js O

INTERMEDIATE C, C++, MATLAB, LATEX, SQL
shell, HTML, Javascript, CSS

BEGINNER Go, Rust, lisp, Java

### **ENGLISH SKILLS**

Able to Listen, Speak, Read and Write English skillfully.

### **SKILLS**

#### Goal Oriented

I believe in action over long-winded discussions. I listen to everyone's viewpoints and use my judgement to immediately act based on consensus to achieve goals quickly and efficiently.

#### Physical Dexterity

Manual manipulation of experimental equipment and training within Black Mesa (e.g. the Hazard Course) have contributed to an enjoyment of working with my hands.

#### Passionate

I have been interested in theoretical physics such as quantum mechanics and relativity from an early age. My education and research have cemented this interest into a pas-

### **PUBLICATIONS**

- Kan Zheng, Lu Hou, Hanling Meng, Qiang Zheng, Ning Lu, Lei Lei, "Soft-defined heterogeneous vehicular network: architecture and challenges," *IEEE Network*, vol. 30, no. 4, July 2016, pp. 72-80.(IF = 7.23)
- 2. Lu Hou, Shaohang Zhao, Xiong Xiong, Kan Zheng, Periklis Chatzimisios, M. Shamim Hossain, Wei Xiang, "Internet of things cloud: architecture and implementation," *IEEE Communications Magazine*, vol. 54, no. 12, Dec. 2016, pp. 32-39. (IF = 10.435)
- **3. Lu Hou**, Shaohang Zhao, Xing Li, Periklis Chatzimisios, Kan Zheng, "Design and implementation of application programming interface for Internet of things cloud," *International Journal of Network Management*, vol. 27, no. 3, June 2016. (IF = 1.118)
- **4. Lu Hou**, Kan Zheng, Periklis Chatzimisios, Yi Feng, "A continuoustime Markov decision process-based resource allocation scheme in vehicular cloud for mobile video services," *Computer Communications*, vol. 118, Mar. 2018, pp. 140-147. (IF = 3.338)
- **5. Lu Hou**, Lei Lei, Kan Zheng, "Design on publish/subscribe message dissemination for vehicular networks with mobile edge computing," *2017 IEEE GLOBECOM*, Dec. 2017
- **6.** Xiong Xiong, **Lu Hou**, Kan Zheng, Wei Xiang, M. Shamim Hossain, and Sk Md Mizanur Rahman, "SMDP-based radio resource allocation scheme in software-defined internet of things networks," *IEEE Sensors Journal* vol. 16, no. 20, June 2016, pp. 7304-7314. (IF = 2.512)
- 7. Xiong Xiong, **Lu Hou**, Long Zhao, "A Group-Based Massive Multiple Access Scheme in Cellular M2M Networks," *Computer Communications*, vol. 121, May. 2018, pp. 44-49. (IF = 3.338)

sion. I greatly enjoy carrying out fundamental physics research with potential practical applications.